(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-02T22:21:13.346795",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Whew~ Another hard day's work done...
Huh? Morning already?
And the weather's actually perfect!
Wow!
I'm so exhausted...
And starving.
Honestly, someone should be making me breakfast right now.
Surely there's someone out there willing to take care of me.
Maybe a little walk will help me recharge.
Then I'll invite someone over.
I don't know.. Who's around at this hour?
I gotta think about this.
Wha- What- Aaaaah!
Oww...
Where am I?
Last thing I remember, I got hit by a car...
Whoa, that's a pretty fancy throne.
Does someone important live here or something?
Ah!
So you're the one who ran me over earlier!
Why were you even driving a car?!
Wait...
you can drive?!
With those tiny little arms and legs?
There's no way you could even reach the pedals!
That's why you messed up and ran me over, isn't it?
You know where we are?
How do you not know?!
It's because of you that I'm stuck in some place I don't even recognize!!
Finally found you!
Kronii, Warden of Time!
What a long journey it's been... Took forever.
You're not about to tell me you don't even know how to get back home... right?
They're really going at it.
Maybe we should join in too!
If you're saying we should sneak in and attack... sure, but
I don't want to join.
But we can take them down while they're distracted by fighting!
Gigi! CC!
So, one of the Kronies ran me over with a car, and
when I came to, I was here!
...was here!
Do you know where this place is?
Why does she know who we are?
And what's a "Kronie," anyway?
She doesn't seem to know where she is, but...
isn't she supposed to be the boss here?
Yeah...
and she kinda looks weak...
What's going on...? What?
Let's beat her and become heroes!
Huh?! Huh?!
Argh! Die, scum! Die! Now!
Die!
Okay, that's a little too far. Hey!
you filthy, filthy, filthy...
Okay, you need to chill out. What?
Kill her! Kill her! Kill her!
Don't kill me!
What? Wait, w-why are you even attacking me?
I mean, you're the boss here, right?
We came here to become heroes!
Huh? Ah, so we're playing hero and villain. Okay.
Okay, I get you.
Playing? It's... It's real!
Okay. Yeah, sure.
Then if I win,
I want you two to cook for me
and then take care of me, meow~!
Uh-ew... I don't... no thank you.
Don't worry, kitten. I'll take care of you.
Ha ha ha!
Okay, I don't want to be your pet.
Oh!
Ha ha ha!
Loser.
One?!
Ha ha ha!
There was one damage.
Even for pretend play...
Okay...
why are your attacks stronger than mine?
Wow, you're pretty weak for a boss, aren't you?
And, no, she does the right amount of damage for a kitten.
Ha ha ha!
Die!
Oh. Okay, you can stop.
Okay. Um, am I really the boss?
Why are you two my enemies?
I just want to go home.
ddyaahhuuuu uaaaa...
Something suddenly feels really bad!
Stand behind me. It's okay, I'll tank it.
The...? What? What is this?
Magic is suddenly... coming out on its own!
Okay, don't! Why did you take it that way?!
No, BAD! Argh!
No! Oh, Aaah!
Uh, I actually beat them.
Oh. What was that just now?
Am I... am I just really goated?
I'm really strong.
But why did it happen on its own?
I won, but now there's nobody left to pamper me.
(Unhappy?)
If you're dealing with a lotta woes
(Unlucky?)
Then you gotta listen very close
(Be happy)
Keep on trying, never give up
(Undead, oh) Don't forget that you're alive
The past you have been running from
That boring future yet to come
Still counseling you, oh my, oh my
Universal peace, peace, yeah
(Unhappy?)
(Unlucky?)
(Be happy)
(Undead, oh, undead, oh, undead, oh, oh, oh)
Hey, hey, hey, hey, somehow feeling like
There's a fight within and it's been going on so long
I don't feel it and (don't even wanna try)
Past version of me (of me, of me, of me)
And those figures of the old
Transparent ghosts over my route
The childish and painful memories
Have the deepest roots
(Saddening?) Nowhere to be seen
(Say what?) Way better than irony
They all see the me of the past
When looking at me now
(Nonsense) Label I can't erase
(Yes) In essence, a complex
It's almost like something's possessing me
It is wrapping tight around
And won't loosen its bounds
The self I used to be before (undead, oh)
Still alive, time is a chain of your own path
To be alive is to always embrace your inner changes, on and on
Don't settle for unhappiness, don't be complacent in distress
Not even trying to seize the joy and be happy, you coward
Oh, this world, oh, this world is one odd, one odd fantasy
Who knows what is coming up next, a monster or a snake?
This is a story starting after that encounter, finally
With people or monsters and spirits, back on topic, peace, peace, yeah
Past and future
Can't change the past
Run for the future
feeling inside
There's nothing left to view
Lived long enough, nothing is new
No sign of anything wonderful waiting down the line
Saddening
too much knowledge
results in feeling like every myth is but another boring evolution
Thrill is what I really want now
bored and down, used to frowns
And this is the way the guidance grew
rising compliance too
It's like I'm going under a lid
I consumed everything
this one or that one or, whichever
and now it all just tastes the same
UNDEAD, oh
still alive
time is a chain of your own path
In any era, your past and your future are in this very moment
Fulfill the life you're set upon, and truthfully keep moving on
Go for that happy ending
UNDEAD, oh
still alive
I'm telling this to you, now
So never give up on pursuing your happiness and keep being human
'Cause being numb to suffering
always enduring everything
it's almost as if you're dead
A lot of corpses
UNDEAD
Unhappy? If you're dealing with a lotta woes
unlucky? Then you gotta listen very close
Be happy! Keep on trying, never give up
Be aware that you're alive
Drowning deep in unhappiness or seizing that true happiness
it's on you, on you, it's all on you
Universal all embracing all creations
Universal, all-embracing, all creation's
Peace, peace yeah!
Past & future
can't change the past
run for the future
Where people gather and go
you'll find all worries and woes
Oh, you gotta live on through this tale
of monsters everywhere that you can see
ああああああああああああ
Lyrics, Music: 梨本うい
[AaAaAaAAaAaAAa
Lyrics, Music: Nashimoto Ui]
あなた
You,
わたし
and me,
ふたり
just the two of us,
ぼっち
all alone.
みらい
Into the future,
くらい
dark as it is,
どこへ
where
いこか
shall we go?
悲しみが壊れて死にそーだ
Sadness shatters, I feel like I'm gonna die.
星空に泣き声が響くのさ
A crying voice echoes through the starry sky.
ああああああああああああ
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
ひろい
In this vast
せかい
world,
なにを
what
うたおか
shall I sing?
悲しみがあふれて泣きそーだ
Sadness overflows, I feel like crying.
握りしめたその手が冷たくて
The hand I gripped tightly is so cold.
ああああああああああああ
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
あっ、あっ、あっ
Ah, ah, ah
悲しみが壊れて死にそーだ
Sadness shatters, I feel like I'm gonna die.
星空に泣き声が響くのさ
A crying voice echoes through the starry sky.
悲しみがあふれて泣きそーだ
Sadness overflows, I feel like crying.
君の声が彼方に消えていく
Your voice fades away into the distance.
ああああああああああああ
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
I turned both of them into undead...
Eyyy!
I thought I'd finally been reunited with my friends, too.
And now I'm all alone in this gloomy place.
Hm? What's this?
My name... HP...
Oh, is this one of those typical status screens?
Oh, I've seen these. I've seen these. I've seen these.
Wait, I love this.
Okay. Let's see. What's it say?
Okay, Kronii. Likes sleep, yeah. Okay, that makes sense.
Oh, pet play...?
Oh, what?
Since when did I become a pet?
I'm not even into those.
I should be the owner.
Not that I'm into that to begin with,
but, that's scary.
It's like someone's weird fantasy got mixed in here.
That's not mine.
Oh, okay.
And there's even a keyword for recording the story.
Everyone watching this,
make sure to use that keyword when you document it
and share it with other people, okay?
Well. And. Oh, yeah. Another thing.
That magic from earlier?
I know you guys are the ones giving the commands.
What kind of person would make me cast something like that at my friends?!
But it was really powerful, wasn't it?
Oh, it completely caught me off guard.
Oh. With magic like that, I can beat anybody.
And even if I could, I wouldn't wanna use it on my friends.
That would suck.
Oh. I wonder how I'm supposed to get back home.
I just want to eat someone's cooking already!
Oh. And I've been trying my best, so I want everyone to praise me, too.
Meow!
I'm crashing out.
Oh. If I'm the boss of this place, that means...
that means I can sit in that throne, right?
Oh, that's so cool.
Wait. I'm so excited.
Okay. Well, for now, I'm just going to sit in the chair and take a break.
Yeah. Okay.
マインドブランド
[Title: Mind Brand]
Welcome to the mindfuck
まてよ そこゆく嬢さん
Wait a minute, young lady walking by,
逆子宿らせ
harboring a breech baby,
あどけの足らない そんな身体に
in that body lacking innocence.
ただしく回らん
With a slow-witted head
愚図の頭で
that doesn't work right,
天真爛漫！
so naive and innocent?!
ほざくな馬鹿め。
Shut your mouth, you fool.
まちな そこゆく兄さん
Hold on, young man walking by,
何の片割れ？
what's your other half?
ちいさなあの娘の 御花を咲かせ、
Plucking the flower of that little girl,
指きりげんまん 星の彼方へ
pinky promise and off beyond the stars,
陽関三畳！？
reciting a parting poem?!
くたばれ雑魚め。
Drop dead, you small fry.
「いついつ出やるの？かごめよかごめ」
"When, oh when will you come out? Kagome, Kagome"
嫌味をからげて 嗤うあなたへ
To you laughing with sarcasm,
ぴたりと重ねて 吐き出す情け
closely pressing together, spitting out pity.
誰もがやがては 地獄の奥底へ
Soon enough, everyone to the depths of hell
連れて行かれる
will be dragged away.
あー、触れあって
Ah, touching each other,
埋めあって
filling each other's voids,
勝ち取った幸せを
the happiness that was won,
盗られた正義のヒーローが泣いている。
the robbed hero of justice is weeping.
抱きあって
Holding each other,
叩きあって
striking each other,
分ちあったあの頃を、
that time when we shared everything...
忘れてしまえたら どれほど楽だろうか。
How much easier would it be if only I could forget?
Welcome to the mindfuck
擦り切れた肌かさぶた
Scraped skin and scabs,
狂かれた山場 愛しさ交えて
a crazy climax mixed with tenderness,
痛む片腹 またまたわがままばかなまさか？
splitting my sides laughing, again with the selfish foolishness, no way?
まだまだながながまなばなきゃだな！
Still a long, long way to go, gotta keep learning!
まだだな
Not yet...
そろそろみんなに？「追いつかないと！」
It's about time I... "catch up to everyone!"
うわごと混じりに？「彷徨う回路！」
Mixed with delirium? "A wandering circuit!"
視界を滲ませ？「はかどる迷子！」
Blurring my vision? "A lost child making headway!"
誰もが元から 未来の材料へ
Everyone, from the start,
あてられている
is assigned to be material for the future.
あー、着飾って 痛がって もぎとった 幸せを、
Ah, dressing up, feeling the pain, the happiness that was torn away...
盗られた悲劇の ヒロインが泣いている。
The heroine of this tragedy, robbed of it, is weeping.
わけあって かけあって 重ねあった 思い出を、
With reasons, bargaining, and all the piled-up memories...
忘れてしまえたら どれほど楽だろうか。
How much easier would it be if I could just forget it all?
嗚呼...
Ah...
強がったって 嘘はばれるぞ
Even if you act tough, the lie will be exposed.
怖がったって 血は流れるぞ
Even if you're scared, the blood will still flow.
匿った 傷口開くぞ
The hidden wound will reopen.
「嫌がったって 傷は痛むぞ」
"Even if you hate it, the wound will still hurt."
じゃれあって 眺めあって 語りあった あのときを、
Flirting, gazing at each other, talking through the night back then...
思い回しては 悲観に暮れてみる。
Turning it over in my mind, I sink into despair.
駆け寄って 寄り添って 笑いあった あのときを、
Running up, cuddling close, laughing together back then...
いっそきれいに
I'd rather cleanly...
忘れてしまいたいんだ。
just forget it all completely.
嗚呼...
Ah...
Welcome to the mind fuck.
Welcome to the mind fuck. Mind fuck.
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, ready for my show
Okay たちまち 独壇場 Listen, listen
Okay, instantly taking full stage, listen, listen
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, ready for my show
傾け 振り切ろう
Go wild, let's break all limits!
Break it down
ヤーヤーヤーヤーヤー 唱タイム
Yah-yah-yah-yah-yah, showtime!
天辺の御成り ほらおいで 宵をコンプリート
Arrival at the top! Come on over, conquer the night!
オーライ Hell, yeah, yeah, yeah
Alright, hell yeah, yeah, yeah!
だんだんノリノリで超簡単 Brah, brah, brah, pow
Getting into the groove, super easy, brah, brah, brah, pow!
えも言われない Ain't nobody stop (Ha, ha)
Indescribably good, ain't nobody stop, ha, ha!
全土絢爛豪華 Attention 騒ごうか
Gorgeous across the land, attention, shall we make some noise?
意思表示にもうじき衝撃の声高らか 堂々登板
Expressing intent, soon to make a grand entrance with a resounding impact!
もう伽藍洞は疾っくの疾う淘汰
The empty shell has long been eliminated,
Ayd 爛桜花 御出座しだ
Ayd, brilliant blossoms are making their debut!
格好つけてるつもりは No, no
I'm not trying to act cool, no, no,
オートマティックに溢れちゃう本能
It's just my instincts overflowing automatically.
宣う断頭台の上で 燥げ華麗
Proclaiming atop the scaffold, make merry gorgeously!
Da, rat, a, tat... WARNING!
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, ready for my show
バンザイ 遊ぶ気に寿 Shout it out, shout it out
Cheers, celebrate the playful spirit, shout it out, shout it out!
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, ready for my show
はんなり 感情通りに八艘飛び Shout it out, shout it out
Gracefully leaping across eight boats following your emotions, shout it out, shout it out!
(Hey, uh) 食らっちゃいな
(Hey, uh) Take that!
(Hey, ha) Rat, tat, tat, tat, tat (Pull up)
(Hey, uh, wa, wa, wa)
満開 総員一気に とびきり Jump around
In full bloom, everyone all at once, jump around to the max!
Look at me now
皮膚を破りそうな程に跳ねる心臓 くらい感情的仕様
A heart beating so hard it could burst through the skin, such an emotional spectacle!
(Exotic VOX)
イニミニマニモ ご来場からのご来光 かくれんぼしてるその気持ち解放
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe, from your arrival to the sunrise, unleash those feelings playing hide-and-seek!
(理性 アディオス) しゃかりきじみちゃう
(Sanity, adios) Going completely frantic!
蛇腹刃 蛇尾 騙る二枚刃 野心家 嫉妬するようなジュース
Serrated blade, serpent tail, deceitful double-edge, a juice that'd make the ambitious jealous!
たぶらかすな カッとなっちゃ嫌 カルマに至る前に蕩うわ
Don't deceive me, don't lose your temper, I'll be enchanted before reaching karma!
蛇腹刃 蛇尾 騙る二枚刃 野心家 嫉妬するようなジュース
Serrated blade, serpent tail, deceitful double-edge, a juice that'd make the ambitious jealous!
たぶらかすな カッとなっちゃ嫌 十色のバタフライ
Don't deceive me, don't lose your temper, a ten-colored butterfly!
(No escape)
ご存じの通り
As you know,
騒々しい鼓動に絆されて もう止まれない
bound by this clamorous heartbeat, I can't stop anymore!
衝動に塗装し描いた Daybreak
Painting over my impulses, depicting the daybreak!
肺貫通 低音狂
Lung-piercing, bass fanatic!
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, ready for my show
異例の危険度 比類なき活気充満
Unprecedented hazard level, filled with unmatched vigor!
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, ready for my show
いちかばちか 嗚呼
All or nothing, ah!
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, ready for my show
バンザイ 遊ぶ気に寿 Shout it out, shout it out
Cheers, celebrate the playful spirit, shout it out, shout it out!
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, ready for my show
喝采
Acclaim...
巻き起こすために
To stir things up,
Stay
一切合切忘れて Shout it out
Forget everything and shout it out!
Hey!
Woah
右に左まとめて
Left and right, all together,
Rat-tat-tat-tat ほら
Rat-tat-tat-tat, come on!
思いっ切り Clap! Clap!
With all your might, clap! Clap!
なにはともあれご唱和あれ
Whatever happens, chant along!
Shout it out, Shout it out
駄目 駄目 駄目
No, no, no,
脳みその中から
from inside my brain,
「やめろ馬鹿」と喚くモラリティ
"Stop it, you idiot!" screams my morality.
ダーリン ベイビー ダーリン
Darling, baby, darling.
半端なクラブ！と
"Half-baked love!"
きらめき浮き足立つ フィロソフィ
A sparkling, exhilarating philosophy.
死ぬほど可愛い 上目遣い
A cute upward glance that's to die for,
なにがし法に触れるくらい
almost breaking some sort of law.
ばら撒く乱心 気づけば蕩尽
Scattering madness, all squandered before I know it.
この世に生まれた君が悪い
It's your fault for being born into this world.
やたらとしんどい 恋煩い
An awfully painful lovesickness,
バラバラんなる頭とこの身体
my head and body are falling to pieces.
頸動脈からアイラブユーが噴き出て
"I love you"s gushing out from my carotid artery,
アイリスアウト
Iris out.
一体どうしよう
What on earth should I do?
この想いをどうしよう
What should I do with these feelings?
あばらの奥を
In the depths of my ribs,
ザラメが溶けてゲロになりそう
the granulated sugar melts and feels like vomit.
瞳孔バチ開いて溺れ死にそう
My pupils wide open, feel like I'm drowning to death.
今 この世で君だけ大正解
Right now in this world, only you are completely right.
Darlin Baby Darlin
ひっくり返っても勝ちようない
Even if turned upside down, I can't win.
君だけルールは適用外
The rules don't apply to you alone.
四つともオセロは黒しかない
In Othello, all four corners are black.
カツアゲ放題
An all-you-can-extort buffet.
君が笑顔で放ったアバダケダブラ
You fired off an Avada Kedavra with a smile.
デコにスティグマ 申し訳ねえな
A stigma on my forehead, so sorry about that.
矢を刺して 貫いて
Pierce me with an arrow, stab through,
ここ弱点
this is my weak spot.
死ぬほど可愛い 上目遣い
A cute upward glance that's to die for,
なにがし法に触れるくらい
almost breaking some sort of law.
ばら撒く乱心 気づけば蕩尽
Scattering madness, all squandered before I know it.
この世に生まれた君が悪い
It's your fault for being born into this world.
パチモンでもいい 何でもいい
A knockoff is fine, anything is fine.
今君と名付いてる全て欲しい
I want everything that bears your name right now.
頸動脈からアイラブユーが噴き出て
"I love you"s gushing out from my carotid artery,
アイリスアウト
Iris out.
一体どうしよう
What on earth should I do?
この想いをどうしよう
What should I do with these feelings?
あばらの奥を
In the depths of my ribs,
ザラメが溶けてゲロになりそう
the granulated sugar melts and feels like vomit.
瞳孔バチ開いて溺れ死にそう
My pupils wide open, feel like I'm drowning to death.
今 この世で君だけ大正解
Right now in this world, only you are completely right.
Darlin Baby Darlin
Kaela!
Kronii! Finally, someone I know!
Yeah, me too!
Where even are we?
I wanna go home but I can't...
Well, I've been stuck here too, and couldn't find a way back.
But if we can't leave, I figured we might as well enjoy ourselves.
You know, that's a pretty positive attitude, but...
don't you wanna go home?
Of course I do.
Well, you know, come to think of it,
what are you doing here, Kronii?
So apparently I'm some kind of boss here, and I can't leave this place.
..And there's nobody around to spoil on me either.
Oh, you want someone to spoil you?
I can give you some head pats if you like.
Heh...
really?
You're okay with that?
Yeah, sure! Come here! Come here!
Meow!
I was a boss too, but nobody ever came to see me.
I got lonely, so I wanted to leave this world.
You want to leave because you were lonely?
I, I ended up fighting Gigi and CC, and I had no idea what was going on.
Well, nobody came to my place, so I decided to go exploring.
Alright!
Will you fight me too? It sounds fun!
You aren't really listening are you...
A battle is only fun if you enjoy it!
Here I come!
What's wrong with you...
So my weapon is a hammer.
Here I come!
Hya!
Maybe I'll just humor her and get this over with.
What?!
It's no fun if you don't take it seriously!
But if I do, I'll end up defeating you!
It's fine, it's fine. Come on, hit me with it.
Hit it!
Well, don't say I didn't warn you.
Ohooo!
Yeah. See, I told you.
That was awesome!
Huh?
That was amazing!
Oh, you're the amazing one!
Well, that was fun.
So let's stop worrying about this world,
sing, dance,
and have a good time before we head home!
I'm fine with the singing and dancing part,
but isn't this a little sudden?
And how exactly are you planning on getting us home?
Well...
I don't know!
純情？なにそれ 愛情？なにそれ
Innocence? What's that? Affection? What's that?
美味しいの？ねぇ
Is it delicious? Hey,
美味しいの？ってなぁ
I'm asking if it's tasty!
乱暴ダメダメ 感情捨て去り
Violence is a no-no, cast away all emotions
いっせーので ぶっ飛ばすだけ
On the count of three, just blast them away
混沌ブギウギ ハッピー特盛り
Chaos Boogie-Woogie, an extra-large serving of happiness
どんぴしゃいら どんぴしゃいらもう
Right on target, spot-on already
だんだん落ちてく IQくそわろ
My IQ is dropping more and more, lol
いっせーので 死ぬまで踊れ
On the count of three, dance until you die!
完全体の山田
Yamada in perfect form,
無関心なんて ありえない
it's impossible to stay indifferent.
3000体の桑田
3,000 Kuwatas,
のほうがいいかなぁ
would that be better, I wonder?
わがままばかりじゃ 落ち着かない
Being so selfish gives me no peace of mind,
冷や汗が出すぎて 気持ち悪い
sweating cold sweat feels disgusting.
当たり前のことにも 手がつかない
I can't even get around to doing ordinary things,
もうなんて言ったらいい？ ばかりで
constantly wondering what I should even say.
世間体とか 投げ出したい
I want to throw away social appearances,
狂ったように 泣き出したい
I want to burst into tears like crazy,
思いのまま生きて消えていきたいな
I want to live as I please and fade away.
純情？なにそれ 愛情？なにそれ
Innocence? What's that? Affection? What's that?
美味しいの？ねぇ
Is it delicious? Hey,
美味しいの？ってなぁ
I'm asking if it's tasty!
乱暴ダメダメ 感情捨て去り
Violence is a no-no, cast away all emotions
いっせーので ぶっ飛ばすだけ
On the count of three, just blast them away
混沌ブギウギ ハッピー特盛り
Chaos Boogie-Woogie, an extra-large serving of happiness
どんぴしゃいら どんぴしゃいらもう
Right on target, spot-on already
だんだん落ちてく IQくそわろ
My IQ is dropping more and more, lol
いっせーので 死ぬまで踊れ
On the count of three, dance until you die!
1 2 まさかり 3 4 刈り取り
One, two, broadaxe; three, four, reaping
もういいんだってもういいんだってもう
Enough already, I said it's enough already!
ハッピーおかわり Give me ときめき
Seconds on happiness, give me that thrill
いっせーので
On the count of three,
さあ飛び込め
come on, dive in!
混沌ブギウギ 混沌特盛り
Chaos Boogie-Woogie, an extra-large serving of chaos
もういいんだってもういいんだってもう
Enough already, I said it's enough already!
最低奴らのライカミステリー
The lowest scumbags' like a mystery
いっせーので ぶっ飛ばすだけ
On the count of three, just blast them away
混沌ブギウギ ハッピー特盛り
Chaos Boogie-Woogie, an extra-large serving of happiness
どんぴしゃいら どんぴしゃいらもう
Right on target, spot-on already
だんだん落ちてく 人生くそわろ
Life is falling apart more and more, lol
いっせーので 死ぬまで踊れ
On the count of three, dance until you die!
もういいや全部全部ほら 忘れてしまおう
Whatever, let's just forget everything, every bit of it
簡単なことじゃないが 我々ならできるだろう
It won't be easy, but we can do it, right?
なぁ
Right?
Get down
頭でわかっては嘆いた
Understanding it in my head, I lamented
転がってく様子を嗤った
I sneered at the sight of tumbling down
寂しいとか愛とかわかんない
I don't understand loneliness or love
人間の形は投げだしたんだ
I've cast away the human form
抱えきれない 言葉だらけの存在証明を
An overwhelming proof of existence made only of words
この小さな劇場から出らんない
I can't get out of this tiny theatre
気づいたら最後逃げ出したい
Once I realize it, I desperately want to run away
僕ら全員演じていたんだ
All of us were just playing a part
エンドロールに向かってゆくんだ
Heading towards the end credits
さあ皆必死に役を演じて 傍観者なんていないのさ
Come, everyone plays their role frantically—there are no onlookers here
”ワタシ”なんてないの どこに居たって居ないよ
"I" don't exist, no matter where I am, I'm not there
ずっと僕は 何者にもなれないで
Unable to become anyone all this time
僕ら今 さあさあ 喰らいあって
Right now, come on, let's devour each other
延長戦 サレンダーして
In extra time, surrendering
メーデー 淡い愛想 垂れ流し
Mayday, pouring out faint sociability
言の愛憎
and love-hate words
ドラマチックな展開を どっか期待してんだろう
You're probably hoping for some dramatic development
君も YES YES 息を呑んで 采配はそこにあんだ
You too, yes, yes, holding your breath, the direction is right there
ヘッドショット 騒ぐ想いも その心撃ち抜いて
Headshot, shoot right through that restless heart
さあ まだ見ぬ糸を引いて
Come, pull the unseen strings
黒幕のお出ましさ
The mastermind is making an appearance
その目に映るのは
Reflected in those eyes is...
触れたら壊れてしまった
If I touched it, it broke completely,
間違ってく様子を黙った
and I stayed silent as things went wrong.
僕ら全員無垢でありました
We were all completely innocent,
いつのまにやら怪物になったんだ
but before we knew it, we became monsters.
その全てを肯定しないと前に進めないかい
Can't we move forward without accepting all of that?
『まあ君にはきっと無理なんだ』
"Well, it's surely impossible for you,"
「だから君にはきっと無理なんだ」
"That's why it's surely impossible for you."
いつのまにやら外野にいたんだ
Before I knew it, I was on the sidelines,
そんなガヤばっかり飛ばしてきたんだ
just constantly hurling heckles like that.
皆必死に自分を守って
Everyone desperately protects themselves,
救いの手を待ってるのさ
waiting for a helping hand.
考えたくはないよ
I don't want to think about it,
馬鹿になっていたいもん
'cause I just want to stay a fool.
ずっと僕は 何者にもなれないで
I've always been unable to become anyone...
だから今 前線上に立って
So now, standing on the front lines,
その旗は高く舞って
that flag flutters high.
劣勢 頼る相棒 言葉すらいらないよ
At a disadvantage, trusting my partner—no words are needed.
ドラマチックな展開はドットヒートしてくだろう
The dramatic development will surely heat up to the max!
君も YES YES 息を呑んで
You too, YES YES, hold your breath,
再会を誓いあって
and let's swear to meet again!
ワンチャンスしかない僕の一瞬を懸けるのさ
I'll wager everything on this one instant, my only shot!
クライマックスみたいな 手に汗を握るのさ
Like a climax, my hands are sweating with suspense!
ぽつりと呟いた
I muttered softly to myself...
隠してきた真実はどこにもない
The truths I've hidden away are nowhere to be found,
嗤ってきた奴らに居場所はない
and there's no place for those who mocked me.
思い出してぽいってして感情はない
Remembering and tossing it away, there are no emotions left.
流した涙 理由なんてない
For the tears that fell, there's no reason at all.
優しさに温度も感じられない
I can't even feel warmth in kindness anymore,
差し伸べた手に疑いしかない
harboring nothing but suspicion for outstretched hands.
穴が空いて愛は垂れてしまいになったんだ
A hole opened up, and love ended up dripping away.
倒れそうな僕を覗き込んだんだ
You peered in at me as I was about to collapse.
諦めかけた人の前にアンタは
Before someone on the verge of giving up, you...
いつもあざ笑うようにおでましさ
...always appear as if to mock them.
君にはどんな風に見えてるんだい
How does it look through your eyes?
呼吸を整えてさ
Catching my breath...
さあ ずっと僕は 何者にもなれないで
Come on, I've always been unable to become anyone...
僕ら今さあさあ 喰らいあって
Here we are now, devouring each other!
延長戦 サレンダーして メーデー
Overtime match, surrender now, mayday!
淡い愛想 垂れ流し 言の愛憎
Spilling faint pleasantries, love and hate of words,
ドラマチックな展開をどっか期待してんだろう
somewhere deep down, you're expecting a dramatic twist!
君も YES YES 息を呑んで
You too, YES YES, hold your breath,
采配は そこにあんだ
the command is right there!
ヘッドショット 騒ぐ想いも その心撃ち抜いてさ
Headshot! Shoot right through that heart and buzzing feelings!
まだ見ぬ糸を引いて 黒幕のお出ましさ
Pulling unseen strings, the mastermind makes their entrance!
その目に映るのは
What is reflected in those eyes...?
都合のいい思いを燃やして
Burning away thoughts of convenience,
呆れた願いはもう手放した
I've already let go of those exasperated wishes.
裏切りや秘密が漂って ここから動けない
Betrayals and secrets linger in the air, and I can't move from here.
生まれてしまった あるいは壊れすぎてしまった
Born into this, or perhaps broken beyond repair...
あの日 あの場所で ずっと止まったままでいた未来
That day, in that place, a future that remained frozen in time.
それでも心のどこかで君を感じていた
Even so, somewhere deep in my heart, I still felt you.
許せない 今の僕は誰？
Unforgivable... who am I right now?
ねえ ずっとずっとそばにいたんだ 「勘違いだ」って 嘘じゃないよ
Hey, I was always by your side—saying "it's a mistake" isn't a lie.
望んだものじゃなくとも あなたに出会えた
Even if it wasn't what I wished for, I was able to meet you.
痛みだけが愛だって信じられるように
So that I can believe this pain alone is love...
僕に触れないで 祈るセレナーデ
Don't touch me—a praying serenade.
僕なしで上手く幸せになってね
Please find a way to be happy without me.
誰よりもずっと 何を手放しても
More than anyone, no matter what I let go of,
これが愛だって信じていた 罰をください
I believed this was love—please give me my punishment.
誰でもない あなた あなただけ
No one else, just you, only you.
世界がまだ忘れてくれなくても
Even if the world refuses to forget me yet,
きっとまだ あなた あなただけ
surely still, it's you, only you.
願い疲れても歌うよ セレナーデ
Even worn out from wishing, I'll sing: serenade.
シナリオ通りのコメディ 不幸自慢はハウメニー？
A comedy right on script—how many boasts of misfortune?
エゴイスティックに光った瞳の中に映ってる あなたは誰？
Reflected in those egotistically shining eyes, who are you?
暗闇が光らせた舞台の上で 何も知らずにただ踊っていられたならよかった
On the stage illuminated by darkness, if only I could've danced knowing nothing.
希望も不幸も身勝手だ 僕ら全員共犯者だった
Hope and misfortune are both selfish; we were all accomplices.
疑う余地もないほど 運命が定まったあの夜から 僕は愛し方を忘れた
Since that night when fate was sealed beyond doubt, I forgot how to love.
これだけ願って これだけ祈って こんな悲しい結末でごめんね
After wishing this much, praying this much—I'm sorry for such a sad ending.
すべて失って すべて消え去っても
Even if I lose everything and everything fades away,
ただ君がずっと生きていた痛みが欲しい
I just want the pain that proves you truly lived.
あと何回数えたら あと何回傷つけば
How many more times must I count? How many more times must I be hurt?
あと何回失えば あと何回壊れ...
How many more times must I lose? How many more times must I break...?
あと何回数えたら
How many more times must I count,
あと何回傷つけば
how many more times must I be hurt,
あと何回失えば
how many more times must I lose something,
この想いは満たされ
before these feelings are fulfilled?
これだけ願って
I wished this much,
これだけ祈って
I prayed this much,
こんな悲しい結末でごめんね
I'm sorry it's such a sad ending.
全て失って
Even if I lose everything,
全て間違いでも
even if it was all a mistake,
ただ僕がずっと愛していた君よ
you, whom I have always loved,
消えないで祈るセレナーデ
a serenade praying you don't disappear.
昔出逢った 幸せになってね
To the you I met back then, please be happy.
誰よりもずっと
More than anyone else,
どんなに手を放しても
no matter how we let go of each other's hands,
これが愛だって信じてた
I believed this was love.
罰をください
Please punish me.
誰でもない あなた あなただけ
No one else, but you, only you.
世界がまだ 忘れてくれなくても
Even if the world won't forget yet,
きっとまだ あなた あなただけ
surely still, you, only you.
願い疲れても歌うよセレナーデ
Even tired of wishing, I'll sing this serenade.
雨が降り去っても
Even after the rain falls and passes,
僕じゃ駄目だって
even if I wasn't the right one,
願い疲れても歌うよセレナーデ
even tired of wishing, I'll sing this serenade.
Kronii!
I've come to save you!
I knew it, Subaru-senpai!
How'd'ya I needed help?
How'd you know I needed help?
I've been watching the whole time!
The whole time...?
Yeah.
And me?
I watch you.
I watched you.
Oh, okay. That's scary, but...
The why?!
Why?!
I, I wish you helped me a lot sooner then!
I wish you helped me a lot sooner then!
Well, you started having fun halfway through,
so I figured I'd see how things played out!
Yeah.
I watched...
just the...
world.
Oh, yeah. The world. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I guess I did end up enjoying parts of it.
See?!
That's why I was wondering whether you actually needed saving!
Aw... well thank you, I guess,
but can you really help me get out of here?
Just...
Please wait. Just...
where are you looking?
Just one more song.
If you sing and dance your heart out,
you can go home!
Really? Yay!
Just watch the world!
The world!
Oh, so that's the world.
やべー
Oh no...
Oh, okay. Wait. Sorry. I was so fascinated.
Please staff, please staff
Down up up up up up up.
Yeah, yeah!
Really?!
Kaela disappeared after fighting and singing, right?
Yeah.
That's because she went back to the original world.
After fighting and singing?
Wait, does that mean I have to fight too?
Yep!
Oh...
I don't get it!
Why do we have to fight at all?!
Think of it like some kind of ritual!
Okay, then we just stand there and take the hit,
and when we get back to the real world,
you're going to make me food and spoil me!!!
やばい！やばい！やばい！やばい！やばい！やばい！
This is bad! This is bad! This is bad! This is bad!
Stop! Please stop please stop please.
YOU!
Are you okay?!
Are you out of your mind?!
Are you okay?
No.
Wait, why should I cook for you?!
And besides, you were already getting spoiled earlier!
Anyway!
You should have fun!
Joy is the key!
You sure about that?
Then you have to entertain me.
Meow!
Eh? Meow?
Huh? Meow?
Are you okay...?
No.
Anyway!
I summon Subatomo!
Come on!
Subatomo is soooo cute!
Subatomo is so cute!
This is "super cute" right? Right?
This is "super cute," right?
Yeah, but it's so tiny.
Tiny?
It's so small.
Yeah! Small is cute!
Just looking at it makes you happy, right?
Just looking at it make you happy, right? Yeah?
Just looking at it makes you happy, right? Yeah?
Yeah, I mean, it's very adorable, but...
...I'm...
I'm also right here too.
Meow~
Meow meow~
クローニーもマジで可愛い！
Kronii is super cute, too!
But, but this is...
これなに？
What is this?
シャイ シャイ クローニー？
Shy Shy Kronii?
No! No, stoppppp!
え、でも、クローニーはにゃーなの？
Is Kronii a meow?
Um... I-I-it's fine.
If you don't know, then, never mind.
It's... it's whatever.
That's... way too creepy, Kronii!
HEY what's that mean?!
Today Kronii is a little, little, are you okay?
Today Kronii is a little... Are you okay?
Are you okay? 大丈夫？
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Hey, that's... I'm never okay. But you shouldn't say that!
Anyway, aren't we supposed to fight though?
Ah, yeah! All right!
Subatomo are you okay?
Go Subatomo!
Yeah! Attack! Go go go go go! Attack! Attack!
You!!
Come! Back back back back!
Are you okay? 大丈夫？
Are you okay?
Subatomo... なんか... ちょっと弱いかもー
Subatomo... might be a little underwhelming...
This lil guy's a weakling. ウィークかもこいつ
This lil guy's a weakling.
Well, I guess I should start getting prepared.
It doesn't even hurt.
Not even a tickle. Sorry.
Not even tickle. Sorry.
This is bad! Really bad! やばいぞ！やばい！
This is bad! Really bad!
Subatomo!!
We're taking this one together!
Oh no! Oh no!
もう身代わりだよお前が！
You're my shield now!
Please, mercy! Please, mercy! Please!
Here I go...
Please mercy!
Waaah!
そんなのってないよ...
That's terrible...
Yayyy!
I'm sorry, but yayyyyy!
Subatomo----!
大丈夫かスバ友！
Are you okay, Subatomo?
Oh, it's alive, oh, thank god, okay.
大変だった もう
That was rough.
See? You're having fun!
This should probably get you home now!
Good luck!
Yeah! Thank you!
Bye!
Go home!
帰ろうスバ友
Go home, Subatomo!
Bye!
What was that?
I don't really get what's going on, but
apparently I can go home if I sing one last song.
So let's do that.
Wait. What's this?
What? Okay, okay.
Let's go through them one by one from the top.
Maybe they'll be useful for something.
Hmm.
Ouro Kronii 5th Anniversary... Ah!
So these are the merch celebrating my anniversary, ey?
Let's see. I wonder what they've got.
They all seem pretty useful, so let's check it out together.
First up, we got a bucket hat.
The illustration was done by Hama Nashi sensei.
The concept is me being... you guessed it, the final boss!
It's reversible and the artwork looks really cool!
And maybe it would make you feel like it would boost your defense stat!
And next up, we got a random attribute acrylic keychain.
The chibi characters were drawn by Gurin sensei!
I wonder which one you'll get ey ey?
I wonder which one you'll get, ey? Ey, ey?
And after the acrylic keychain, we got a Cushion!
The design for this was also done by Gurin sensei.
The cushion has an illustration on both sides,
and size wise, it's pretty easy to use as well.
and size-wise, it's pretty easy to use as well.
Next up, we got this cute Boros Lamp!
Looks like you can adjust the brightness between two levels,
and the design is super duper cute,
you'll be safe even in dark places.
When you're scared he's got you. Don't worry everyone.
And coming up next, we got a situation voice pack!
The title being Villainous Kronii's Final Loop.
Sounds pretty ominous, but, I can't wait to check it out!
I want to check it out I wanna listen to it already!
And finally, if you purchase everything,
...if you purchase everything,
you'll also receive a cheki-style card with a foil stamped signature,
along with a bonus voice pack.
The card illustration was drawn by, you guessed it, Hama Nashi sensei.
And as for the bonus voice pack,
it's going to be telling the story of joining hands and heading into the final battle in order to bring the loop to an end.
It's going to be very emotional, so go check it out.
Once more, here is the full line up.
Yeah, every single one of these looks like they'd help me escape this other world,
so I definitely want to get them all.
And, with that, looks like that's everything.
So, according to Subaru senpai, all I have to do is sing one more song. So,
whew. Here goes. Let me try it.
恋 / Lyrics, Music: 星野源
[Song: Koi | Lyrics & Music: Gen Hoshino]
営みの 街が暮れたら 色めき
The bustling streets come alive as dusk falls,
風たちは運ぶわ カラスと人々の群れ
and the winds carry along the flocks of crows and people.
意味なんかないさ 暮らしがあるだけ
There's no deep meaning, we're just living our lives.
ただ腹を空かせて 君の元へ帰るんだ
Just getting hungry, and heading home to you.
物心ついたらふと 見上げて思うことが
When I grew up, looking up, I suddenly realized
この世にいる誰も 二人から
that everyone in this world begins from two people.
胸の中にあるもの
What's inside your heart,
いつか見えなくなるもの
what will one day fade from sight...
それは側にいること
That is being by your side,
いつも思い出して
always remember that.
君の中にあるもの
What's inside of you,
距離の中にある鼓動
the heartbeat within the distance...
恋をしたの貴方の
I fell in love with your
指の混ざり 頬の香り
entwined fingers and the scent of your cheek.
夫婦を超えてゆけ
Let's go beyond being husband and wife!
みにくいと 秘めた想いは 色づき
Feelings hidden away as unsightly begin to color,
白鳥は運ぶわ 当たり前を変えながら
and the swans carry them, changing what we took for granted.
恋せずにいられないな
I can't help but fall in love,
似た顔も虚構にも
with familiar faces, even with fiction...
愛が生まれるのは 一人から
Love is born from just one person.
胸の中にあるもの
What's inside your heart,
いつか見えなくなるもの
what will one day fade from sight...
それは側にいること
That is being by your side,
いつも思い出して
always remember that.
君の中にあるもの
What's inside of you,
距離の中にある鼓動
the heartbeat within the distance...
恋をしたの貴方の
I fell in love with your
指の混ざり 頬の香り
entwined fingers and the scent of your cheek.
夫婦を超えてゆけ
Let's go beyond being husband and wife!
泣き顔も
Tearful faces,
黙る夜も
silent nights,
揺れる笑顔も
and wavering smiles,
いつまでも
forever and ever,
forever and ever...
胸の中にあるもの
What's inside your heart,
いつか見えなくなるもの
what will one day fade from sight...
それは側にいること
That is being by your side,
いつも思い出して
always remember that.
君の中にあるもの
What's inside of you,
距離の中にある鼓動
the heartbeat within the distance...
恋をしたの貴方の
I fell in love with your
指の混ざり 頬の香り
entwined fingers and the scent of your cheek.
夫婦を超えてゆけ
Let's go beyond husband and wife,
二人を超えてゆけ
let's go beyond just the two of us,
一人を超えてゆけ
let's transcend ourselves!
Where am I?
I'm back!
...or was I asleep?
Was it all a dream?
I dunno.
Oh, my back. Oh, I'm getting old.
That was such a weird experience.
Oh, yeah! I was going to invite someone over to my place.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then I was going to ask them to make me something to eat.
Oh, wait. No. I'm being— I'm still being arrogant.
That's not asking. That's giving an order.
Which damn right I should.
No, I should be nicer about this. Um...
Make me some food, please. Meow~
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, that's... That's cute.
Yeah, that's more like it. Yeah.
Or not. What are they going to do, huh?
Oh, sorry. Been a long day.
Who am I even talking to?
Anyway... Um, yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
Who should I invite?
Is there going to be someone around at this hour?
I gotta think about this...
Oh, what the fu----! Aaaahh!
I Reincarnated as a Villainess?! Ouro Kronii 3th Anniversary LIVE
[Title: I Reincarnated as a Villainess?! Ouro Kronii 3rd Anniversary LIVE]